repost.us 2011-11-08

# Privacy Policy | Repost.Us

Last updated: March 2011

Free Range Content, Inc. (“FRC”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy has been prepared to describe the information we collect about you, how it is used, and with whom we may or may not share it. This Privacy Policy covers the Free Range Content website, any content provided on the website or through Repost.Us, along with any and all related websites (including blogs), and any website registration, survey, and polling pages that we may create for other entities. 

This Privacy Policy applies to FRC services only, and does not apply to any sites not controlled by FRC that may link to or from the FRC website, including content from third-party publishers or any third-party applications, gadgets, or clickable advertisements on our site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other such parties / sites. We do not exercise control over the sites that appear as search results when you use the FRC website. 

## Registration

You must register for an account on this site in order to use certain of the site’s services, such as syndicating or republishing content. By Registering with FRC, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. You may browse the FRC site without registering.

## Your Information and Our Use

In order to provide you with our technology, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Personal Information: When you register for an account, you will be asked to provide your name, email address, a user name, a password, and other personally identifying information (collectively, “Personally Identifiable Information”). You may select any username you want, except that your username cannot be an impersonation, the same or confusingly similar to a famous trademark, or be a term that is offensive in any way. You may, but are not obligated to, use your own name. If you do use your own name, you consent to it being passed to others by use of the functions of this site. FRC reserves the right to reject or remove any username that does not meet applicable standards. Please note that your Personally Identifiable Information, in addition to other demographic data, will be retained in order to allow you to use your account. It is our policy to use Personally Identifiable Information to provide our technology and services, and not to provide Personally Identifiable Information to anyone outside of FRC without your consent (but see “Exceptions to this Privacy Policy” below). 
  * Submitted Material: When you use the FRC website, Repost.Us, and functionality, you will provide certain materials and content. As you participate in the website, you will also provide certain information regarding such participation to us. As a reminder, whenever you share information on FRC in your profile, in public areas, or with specific individuals, such information can be viewed by such persons.
  * Public Content: If you provide content to FRC for public view, we may distribute that content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their websites and other media platforms. FRC may, in some instances, ask that such third parties credit you as the source of these contributions, and will provide your account name and profile photo, if any, to them for such purpose.
  * Website Visit Information: When you visit our website, we may create a log of your visit with information, which includes information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address; URL information; browser type and language; and the date, time, and duration of your visit. 
  * Links: The FRC website may present links in a format that permits us to track whether these links have been followed. We will use this tracking information to help improve the quality of our custom content, search technology, and advertising.
  * Cookies: When you visit our website, we may send cookies (little files for your browser that identify your browser and your visit). FRC also uses cookies in its advertising services in order to help publishers and advertisers manage and provide advertising across the web.
  * Communications: If you send us emails, faxes, letters, or other communications, we may keep these in order to address your issue.
  * Third Party Content: FRC may make available third-party content, applications and information for syndication from participating publishers. The information collected by FRC when you enable or use content from third-party publishers is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information or content collected by third-party publishers when you use their content or applications is governed by their privacy policies. Please be sure to review the privacy policies of any third-party publisher if you enable or use their content. 
  * Tax Information. If you are a Publisher (as defined in the Content License Agreement), we may collect certain tax information from you in order for us to make proper tax filings. We will not use or disclose such tax information except as necessary for FRC to make proper tax filings.

The information we collect, as described above, will be used pursuant to this Privacy Policy, and for the following purposes: to improve our services and products; to develop new services; to ensure and improve the technical functionality of our website and network; to protect your rights, FRC’s rights, and the rights of other FRC users; and to assist FRC in providing you with services (including customizing the content and advertising provided to you). FRC may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to make any filings or reports required by the IRS for tax purposes. If we use your Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different than the purposes for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

## Third Party Publishers – Information Sharing

FRC operates Repost.Us, an instant syndication platform that allows third-party publishers to automatically make their content available at all times to a broad range of syndicators. FRC may provide your Personally Identifiable Information at the request of such third-party publishers but only to the extent that you use such third-party publisher’s content. FRC employees and agents will not share your Personally Identifiable Information except as required to adequately provide services to such third party publishers. FRC will not sell or provide any information to a third party, including other third-party publishers’ clients that may employ the services of FRC, other than as provided herein.

## Blogs

FRC may host blogs or search field topics that gather visitor demographic data including names and email addresses. FRC may use this information to provide updates about our website and our services. FRC will not resell or provide this information to any third-party vendors.

## Communications With Others

This site may allow you to contribute to one or more blogs or to communicate by means of online functions. Nothing requires you to disclose your identity to others. If you choose to disclose your identity to third parties using any site function or service, you do so at your own risk. FRC is not responsible for the privacy or security of any information, personal or otherwise, that you may choose to communicate or exchange using the functionality of this site. Each item of information or any materials you contribute for such purposes is your “Public Content.” Public Content must be content and information that you have a right to disclose and transfer and must not violate any other person’s privacy or intellectual property rights.

## Exceptions to this Privacy Policy

In certain circumstances, FRC may release the information it collects, for the following purposes:

  * to respond to court orders, subpoenas, or other legal process, or to help FRC in establishing or exercising its legal rights or defend itself against legal claims;
  * to investigate, prevent, or take action with regard to illegal activity, suspected fraud, potential threat to the physical safety of any individual, violations of the FRC Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law;
  * to investigate or take action with respect to any circumstance that could expose FRC to liability; and
  * if FRC is acquired by or merges with another company. In this event, FRC will undertake its best efforts to notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

FRC may also share non-personal information about you, in the aggregate, to third parties.

## Information Security

FRC will use its best efforts to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data, but cannot guarantee the security of its website or Repost.Us. In order to ensure the continued security of its website and Repost.Us, FRC will need you to assist in preventing security breaches by committing to the following:

  * You will not send or otherwise post unauthorized commercial communications (such as spam) to others in connection with your use of FRC’s website or Repost.Us;
  * You will not collect the content of third party publishers or information, or otherwise access FRC’s website or Repost.Us using automated means (such as harvesting bots, robots, spiders, or scrapers) without FRC’s permission;
  * You will not post content that is hateful, threatening or pornographic, incites violence or contains nudity or graphic or gratuitous violence in connection with your use of FRC’s website or Repost.Us;
  * You will not use FRC’s website or Repost.Us to do anything unlawful, misleading, malicious, or discriminatory; and
  * You will not facilitate or encourage any violations of this Privacy Policy.

## Special Provisions Applicable to Developers/Operators of Content or Websites

If you are a developer or operator of content or website, the following additional terms may apply to you:

  * FRC gives you all rights necessary to use the code, APIs, data, and tools you receive from us.
  * You will not sell, transfer, or sublicense our code, APIs, or tools to anyone.
  * You will not misrepresent your relationship with FRC to others.
  * You may use the logos FRC makes available to developers or issue a press release or other public statement so long as you follow FRC’s Terms of Use.
  * FRC can issue a press release describing FRC’s relationship with you.
  * We can analyze your content and data for any purpose, including commercial (such as for targeting the delivery of advertisements and indexing content for search).
  * We can create applications and content that offer similar features and services to; or otherwise compete with, your content or applications.

## Our Policy Toward Children

The FRC website is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children younger than eighteen years of age in the United States. In connection with your use and access of FRC’s website or Repost.Us, you represent that you are of contractual legal age under the laws of your jurisdiction. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California, under the California Civil Code, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the Company has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes and a disclosure of the shared information. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that provides you with an “opt-out” choice for use of your personal information by third parties for marketing purposes, the Company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

This site qualifies for the alternative option. Its privacy policy provides you with information on how you may opt-out from the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your personal information during the preceding year for marketing purposes.

If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third-party disclosure choices, send a request to the following email address [privacy@freerangecontent.com](mailto:privacy@freerangecontent.com).

## Dispute Resolution

If you believe that FRC has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please write to us at the following address:

> Free Range Content, Inc.  
>  Attention: Legal Department – Privacy Policy Dispute Resolution  
>  506 Baker Street,  
>  San Francisco, CA 94117 USA 

If we receive any formal, written complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, we will seek to contact you to address your concerns.

Note: This address is provided exclusively for notifying us about the Privacy Policy. Inquiries regarding any other topics, such as technical support requests, reports concerning email abuse, and reports of instances of piracy, will not receive a response through this process.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

FRC may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your Personally Identifiable Information by sending a notice to the primary email address you have specified in your FRC account or by placing a prominent notice on the FRC website. 

## Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using this website or Repost.Us, or by submitting demographic information on any online pages that FRC may host on behalf of third parties, you submit your agreement to this Privacy Policy. 

## Termination

If you violate this Privacy Policy or otherwise create risk or possible legal exposure for us, we can stop providing all or partly of your access to the FRC website, Repost.Us or the content made available therein. We will notify you by email or at the next time you attempt to access the website or Repost.Us.
